A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G
1936-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA732C
9281 Microform Reels
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Conditions Governing Access note
Files for Ford Foundation grants made to institutions/organizations that have been closed/inactive for 10 years or more are open for scholarly research. In addition, there is a selection of 8 Grant Files which remain restricted from scholarly access.
Arrangement note
Each Ford Foundation Grant and the corresponding Grant File is identified by a unique Program Action (PA) number. PA numbers begin with the year a grant was made (2-digits), followed by a sequential number within that year (4-digits).
For example: PA 55-0123 was the 123rd grant made in the year 1955. PA numbers are often typed or handwritten on Ford documents in the following format: 55-123 (year)-(####). However, the Ford Foundation’s grants database (LINKS) uses an 8-digit format for PA numbers: 05500123 (0YY#####).
Beginning in the 1970s the 4th digit in the 8-digit PA number was used to encode at least three different types of Ford grants:
0YY5#### = Delegated Authority Grants (DAG) / Delegated Authority Projects (DAP)
0YY6#### = Grants to Individuals
0YY9#### = Foundation Administered Projects (FAP)
After the year 2000 a “1” is used as the first digit in the 8-digit PA number to signify the 21st century. For example the 123rd grant made in 2012 would be PA number 11200123.
Grant Files were not microfilmed in numerical order, and the Ford Foundation’s LINKS database must be used to identify on which microfilm reel (or reels) any specific Grant File is housed.
Other Finding Aids note
Grant Files are indexed in the Ford Foundation’s grants database (LINKS). This database is not available to the public. The Ford Foundation Central Index cards, 1950-1996 (FA736) also provide indexing for Grant Files, and can be searched by institutional/organizational name, personal name, grant location, and subject. Grant Files from 1953 to 1974 are also listed by PA number in the Fund File Index.
Arrangement note
Each Ford Foundation Grant File is arranged into 4 sections:
Section 1. BASIC DOCUMENTS: Program Action Forms Accepted Proposals Tax Forms an d Certifications Docket Excerpts Request for Grant Action (RGA) Grant Notification Letter & Budget Terms of Grant Grant Acceptance Letter Supplementary Requests & Agreements Modification Requests & Agreements Section 2. PAYMENTS: Requests Letters Acknowledgments Section 3. REPORTS: Grant Status Report Forms Grantee Narrative and Financial Reports Section 4. CORRESPONDENCE: All other correspondence and material, in reverse chronological order
A possible 5th section, ‘ATTACHMENTS’, will contain copies of printed ephemera & clippings related to the grant. Grant Files may also be followed by a ‘Grants Accounting File’ which summarizes the grant.
Also, early Grant Files (roughly 1950-1970) often include a CROSS REFERENCE sheet listing other grants made in a related subject or Program Area, and a ‘BIBLIOGRAPHY of GRANT-RELATED MATERIALS’ at the beginning of the file.
Other Finding Aids
For descriptions of Ford Foundation Grants, please refer to the following findng aids (arranged alphabetically):
FA732A Ford Foundation records, Grants, A-B
FA732B Ford Foundation records, Grants, C-D
FA732D Ford Foundation records, Grants, H-K
FA732E Ford Foundation records, Grants, L-N
FA732F Ford Foundation records, Grants, O-R
FA732G Ford Foundation records, Grants, S-Thel
FA732H Ford Foundation records, Grants, Them-Tw
FA732I Ford Foundation records, Grants, U-Z
Ford Foundation
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Ear Say Inc (10550208), 2004 December 01-2005 December 31 (Reel 9094)
    Grant Purpose
    To launch the tour of the "Crossing the BLVD" exhibition to museums, galleries and educational institutions throughout the United States
    Program Name
    Media Arts and Culture
    Grant Amount
    $50,000.00;$50,000.00
    Program Officer
    Uno, Roberta
    United States; Queens (New York, N.Y.); Ear Say Inc
  - Earlham College (05600478), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0307)
    TO RAISE TEACHERS@ SALARIES IN PRIVATE LIBERAL ARTS AND SCIENCE COLLEGES & UNIVERSITIES IN USA & TERR. %ENDOW. GENERAL SUPPORT
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration
    $245,500.00;$245,500.00
    Earlham College
  - Earlham College (05900331), 1959 July 16-1964 March 28 (Reel 2524;3031)
    DEVELOPMENT OF INTERNATIONAL STUDIES IN THE UNDERGRADUATE CURRICULUM
    International - Office of the Vice President [ID/OVP]
    $310,000.00;$310,000.00
    Barber, Elinor G.
  - Earlham College (06200343), 1962 June 22-1965 June 21 (Reel 0974)
    GENERAL SUPPORT
    Education and Public Policy
    $1,600,000.00;$1,600,000.00
  - Earlham College (06800415), 1968 June 01-1972 May 31 (Reel 1895)
    PROGRAM OF GRANTS-IN-AID AT SELECTED COLLEGES FOR SUPPORT OF FACULTY DEVELOPMENT IN THE HUMANITIES
    $40,000.00;$40,000.00
    Sheldon, Richard C.
  - Earlham College (07300542), 1973 July 01-1976 June 30 (Reel 1569)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR INNOVATION IN UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION
    $150,000.00;$150,000.00
    Crossland, Fred E. (Fred Eugene)
    Indiana; Earlham College
  - Earlham College (08600899), 1986 September 01-1989 August 31 (Reel 5723)
    SUPPORT TO IMPROVE THE QUALITY OF UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION AND RECRUIT FUTURE FACULTY/FUND FOR FACULTY/STUDENT PROJECTS
    Education & Culture Program [EC]
    $250,000.00;$250,000.00
    Stanley, Peter W.
    United States; Earlham College
  - Earlham College (09100745), 1991 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel 7904)
    TO ENCOURAGE UNDERGRADUATES TO PURSUE CAREERS AS PROFESSORS
    $200,000.00;$200,000.00
    Beckham, Edgar F.
  - Early Development Association (07100313), 1971 March 01-1973 June 11 (Reel 1724;1725)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A JAPANESE-AMERICAN EDUCATION LEADERSHIP EXCHANGE PROGRAM
    $113,894.00;$113,894.00
    List, Claire
    Japan; United States; Early Development Association
  - Earth Action Network, Inc. (10250975), 2002 April 15-2002 October 14 (Reel 9037)
    For a special issue of e/The Environment Magazine on ecotourism, to be published in conjunction with the World Ecotourism Summit
    Community and Resource Development
    Conroy, Michael E.
    Global; Sustainable development--Global; Ecotourism--Global; Earth Action Network, Inc.
  - Earth House (10550855), 2005 May 01-2005 December 31 (Reel 9164)
    For a book based on conference papers from the May 2005 second regional equity summit and to document the proceedings and plan the dissemination of the resulting audiotapes and CDs
    $65,000.00;$65,000.00
    Anthony, Carl
    United States; Earth House
  - Earth Island Institute (10102016), 2001 September 01-2003 February 28 (Reel 9108)
    To promote and distribute "In the Light of Reverence," a documentary on Native American struggles to protect landscapes of spiritual significance
    KC & F - Office of the Vice President
    Wilson, Kenneth
    United States; Indians of North America. Indians -- Religion; Earth Island Institute
  - Earth Island Institute (10351911), 2003 October 01-2004 September 30 (Reel 9106)
    Start-up support for the Environmental Education and Horticultural Institute to promote environmentally and socially just practices and healthy lifestyles
    Richmond (Calif.); Earth Island Institute
  - Earth Times Foundation (10102152), 2001 August 01-2001 October 31 (Reel 8991)
    To produce a daily print and web newspaper at the United Nations World Conference Against Racism
    Human Rights
    $125,000.00;$125,000.00
    Cox, Larry
    Global; Race relations--Congresses--Information services; Intergroup relations -- Congresses -- Information services; Earth Times Foundation
  - Earthcare Africa Monitoring Institute (09651160), 1996 August 01-1998 July 31 (Reel 7198;7292)
    ADVOCACY PROJECT ON ECONOMIC RIGHTS OF WOMEN IN EAST AFRICA
    Eastern Africa (Nairobi)
    $75,000.00;$75,000.00
    Moyo, Jonathan N.
    Africa, East; Women--Economic conditions--Africa, East; Women--Political activity--Africa, East; Environmental protection -- Africa, East; Earthcare Africa Monitoring Institute
  - Earthwatch Expeditions, Inc. (08900878), 1989 July 01-1991 June 30 (Reel 5973)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A SOVIET-AMERICAN SCIENTIFIC EXCHANGE PROGRAM ENTITLED MISSION TO EARTH (009)
    Rural Poverty & Resources Program [RPR];International Affairs Program [IA]
    $120,000.00;$120,000.00
    Balaran, Paul;Maughan, Janet;O'Cleireacain, Seamus
    Soviet Union; United States; Earthwatch Expeditions, Inc.
  - East African Centre for Constitutional Development (10051017), 2000 May 01-2003 May 31 (Reel 8965)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH, PUBLICATION, AND WORKSHOP ON THE CONSTITUTION-MAKING PROCESS IN UGANDA
    Eastern Africa (Nairobi);Governance and Civil Society
    $67,000.00;$67,000.00
    Akin Aina, Tade;Pearson, Katharine R.
    Uganda; Constitutions -- Uganda -- Congresses; Democracy -- Uganda --Congresses; East African Centre for Constitutional Development
  - East African Centre for Constitutional Development (10250273), 2001 November 01-2002 October 31 (Reel 9021)
    For a follow-up conference on constitutionalism and transition politics in Africa and Eastern Europe
    Governance and Civil Society;Southern Africa (Johannesburg);Eastern Africa (Nairobi);West Africa (Lagos)
    $160,000.00;$160,000.00
    Ihonvbere, Julius Omozuanvbo;Grudzinska-Gross, Irena;Hawes, Gary A.;Akin Aina, Tade;TBS/PSJ
    Europe, Eastern; Africa; East African Centre for Constitutional Development
  - East African Common Services Organization (06300088), 1963 January 03-1964 June 02 (Reel 0777)
    DEVELOPMENT OF ECONOMIC POLICIES AND PLANNING OPERATIONS IN EAST AFRICA
    $45,000.00;$21,528.38
    East African Common Services Organization
  - East African Common Services Organization (06700159), 1967 March 28-1968 March 27 (Reel 1531;4035)
    CONFERENCE ON WILDLIFE AS A FORM OF LAND USE TO BE HELD BY EAST AFRICAN AGRICULTURE AND FORESTRY RESEARCH ORGANIZATION
    $25,000.00;$25,000.00
    Goodwillie, Susan R.;Scott, Thomas D.
    Kenya; East African Common Services Organization
  - East African Community (07550141), 1974 June 24-1974 September 23 (Reel 1222)
    SUPPORT FOR WEST AFRICAN TRAINERS FOR WORKSHOP ON OBJECTIVE TESTING
    $4,519.00;$4,519.00
    Goodwillie, Susan R.;Smock, David R.
    Africa, East; East African Community
  - East African Community (07650024), 1975 October 01-1976 November 30 (Reel 1256;4089)
    PARTIAL PARTICIPANT COSTS FOR CONFERENCE ON IMPROVING PERFORMANCE IN PUBLIC ENTERPRISES, NOVEMBER 1975
    $3,920.00;$3,837.45
    Anderson, David A.;Goodwillie, Susan R.
    Africa, East; Africa, Southern; East African Community
  - East African Community (07750273), 1977 March 16-1978 March 15 (Reel 1224;4103)
    WORKSHOP ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT, APRIL 1977
    $11,650.00;$10,831.59
    Goodwillie, Susan R.;Remenyi, J. V.;Winans, Edgar V. (Edgar Vincent)
  - East African Community (07950328), 1979 March 19-1979 September 18 (Reel 2218)
    SOCIAL SCIENCE CONSULTATIVE GROUP MEETING, APRIL 1979
    $7,800.00;$4,651.83
    Hyden, Goran S.
  - East African Law Society Limited (09850893), 1998 April 01-1999 March 31 (Reel 8500)
    A SEMINAR ON REGIONAL CONFLICTS AND REFUGEES FOR LAWYERS IN EAST AFRICA
    Gitari, Joseph
    Africa, East; Dispute resolution (Law) -- Africa, Eastern; East African Law Society Limited
  - East African Law Society Limited (10101009), 2001 April 01-2002 March 31 (Reel 8797)
    Support for research, public convenings, and participation of East Africans in the World Conference Against Racism and Xenophobia, and for post-conference activities
    Africa, East; Racism--Global--Congresses; Xenophobia--Global--Congresses; East African Law Society Limited
  - East African Staff College (07450688), 1974 October 01-1974 December 31 (Reel 1219)
    SEMINAR ON PROGRAMME AND PERFORMANCE BUDGETING (PARTIAL COSTS)
    $2,717.00;$2,717.00
    Anderson, David A.;Herman, William A.
    Africa, East; East African Staff College
  - East African Wild Life Society (10150558), 2001 February 01-2003 January 31 (Reel 9103)
    Provision of technical support to Community Forest Management Committees in Kenya
    Menzies, Nicholas K.
    Kenya; Community forestry -- Africa, East; Conservation of natural resources -- Africa, East; East African Wild Life Society
  - East African Wild Life Society (10251894), 2002 September 01-2003 August 31 (Reel 9211)
    To administer a feasibility study for the proposed East African Conservation Trust
    $50,000.00;$21,688.51
    Pearson, Katharine R.
    Africa, East; East African Wild Life Society
  - East Amwell Environment Commission (07350754), 1973 September 05-1975 February 04 (Reel 1423)
    PROJECT WITH ENVIRONMENTAL COMMISSIONS:FRANKLIN, HILLSBOROUGH, RARITAN, AND TEWKSBURY FOR A REGIONAL NATURAL RESOURCES INVENTORY
    $1,000.00;$1,000.00
    Ames, Edward A.
    East Amwell Environment Commission
  - East Asian History of Science Trust (07700643), 1977 September 01-1979 August 31 (Reel 5529)
    TO SUPPORT THE COMPLETION OF JOSEPH NEEDHAM'S MULTI-VOLUME WORK, "SCIENCE AND CIVILIZATION IN CHINA"
    Asia and The Pacific [ASIA]
    $60,000.00;$60,000.00
    Balaran, Paul;Geithner, Peter F.
    China; Science and civilization--History--Asia; East Asian History of Science Trust
  - East Aurora Environmental Commission (07450312), 1974 March 26-1975 March 25 (Reel 1400)
    PREPARATION OF A MASTER SITE DEVELOPMENT PLAN FOR AN OPEN SPACE WILDERNESS AREA IN THE VILLAGE
    $750.00;$750.00
    East Aurora Environmental Commission
  - East Baton Rouge Parish School Board (08700035), 1986 October 01-1987 November 30 (Reel 6034)
    SUPPORT TO ASSIST A SCHOOL AND COMMUNITY COLLABORATIVE TO DEVELOP PLANS AND PROGRAMS TO PREVENT SCHOOL DROPOUTS
    Urban Poverty Program [UP]
    Meade, Edward J.
    Baton Rouge (La.); East Baton Rouge Parish School Board
  - East Baton Rouge Parish School Board (08800239), 1988 January 01-1990 February 28 (Reel 6221)
    SUPPORT TO DIRECTLY AND INDIRECTLY ASSIST SCHOOL COMMUNITY COLLABORATIVES IMPLEMENT PLANS TO PREVENT DROPOUTS
    $70,000.00;$70,000.00
  - East Bay Community Foundation (08901324), 1989 July 01-1991 June 30 (Reel 6469)
    SUPPORT FOR A COALITION OF FUNDERS FOCUSING ON COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT IN DISTRESSED EAST BAY COMMUNITIES
    $100,000.00;$100,000.00
    Brown, Prudence
    Oakland (Calif.); East Bay Community Foundation
  - East Bay Community Foundation (09001460), 1991 January 01-1993 September 30 (Reel 6823)
    SUPPORT FOR A COLLABORATIVE GRANT POOL FOR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT IN DISTRESSED EAST BAY COMMUNITIES
    Kubisch, Anne C.
  - East Bay Community Foundation (10100678), 2001 January 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9207)
    Partial support for East Bay's project to incorporate environmental, economic, and social equity issues in development plans for the Uptown section of Oakland
    $300,000.00;$300,000.00
    Duncan, Cynthia M.
    Oakland (Calif.); Community development -- California -- Oakland (Calif.); City planning -- Environmental aspects; East Bay Community Foundation
  - East Bridgewater Conservation Commission (07350308), 1973 January 30-1974 January 29 (Reel 1452)
    DEVELOPMENT & IMPLEMENTATION OF A RECREATION PLAN FOR 4 1/2 ACRES OF LAND ALONG THE SATUCKET RIVER
    $4,200.00;$4,200.00
    Massachusetts; East Bridgewater Conservation Commission
  - East China University of Politics and Law (09801405), 1998 July 01-2000 June 30 (Reel 8222)
    SUPPORT FOR JUDICIAL REFORM AND JUDICIAL TRAINING
    China (Beijing)
    Liu, Mina
    China; Judges--Education--China; Legal services--China; East China University of Politics and Law
  - East China University of Politics and Law (10350336), 2003 January 01-2005 January 01 (Reel 9239)
    For the continued development of the clinical legal education curriculum
    $35,500.00;$35,500.00
    China; East China University of Politics and Law
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05100022), 1951 (Reel 1193;1195)
    European and International Affairs
    East European Fund, Inc.
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05100040), 1951 (Reel 1193;1195 (PA53-31))
    $585,000.00;$585,000.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05200073), 1952 (Reel 1193;1195(53-31))
    GENERAL SUPPORT (INCLUDES $523,000 FOR CHEKHOV PUBLISHING HOUSE)
    $785,000.00;$785,000.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05200107), 1952 (Reel 1193;1195(53-31))
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05300031), 1953 April 01-1954 September 30 (Reel 1193;1195;5512;5513)
    SUPPORT OF PROGRAM AND IN PARTICULAR ITS PROGRAM OF EDUCATIONAL AND ASSISTANCE TO EXILED GROUPS & ADMINISTRATION
    $558,000.00;$558,000.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05300190), 1953 (Reel 1193;1195 (PA53-31))
    $666,000.00;$666,000.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05300201), 1952 (Reel 1193;1195 (PA53-31))
    $37,500.00;$37,500.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05400011), 1954 March 04-1955 August 31 (Reel 1195;4178)
    $245,000.00;$245,000.00
  - East European Fund, Inc. (05400169), 1953 November 30-1956 September 30 (Reel 1195)
    SUPPORT OF CHEKHOV PUBLISHING HOUSE
    $615,000.00;$615,000.00
  - East Fishkill Environmental Conservation Commission (07350668), 1973 August 16-1974 August 15 (Reel 1421)
    PROJECT TO BE UNDERTAKEN WITH FIVE CONSERVATION COMMISSIONS TO CONDUCT WATER QUALITY SURVEY OF FISHKILL CREEK & MAJOR TRIBUT.
    $700.00;$648.33
    New York (State); East Fishkill Environmental Conservation Commission
  - East Greenwich Conservation Commission (07450619), 1974 September 06-1976 March 05 (Reel 1401)
    WATER QUALITY STUDY OF EAST GREENWICH COVE TO SERVE AS A BASIS FORA POLLUTION ABATEMENT PROGRAM
    $825.00;$825.00
    Lisniewski, Theresa H.
    East Greenwich Conservation Commission
  - East Hanover Township Environmental Commission (07350860), 1973 September 27-1975 March 26 (Reel 1423)
    PREPARATION OF A NATURAL RESOURCE INVENTORY OF THE TOWNSHIP AND DEVEL. OF A REGIONAL PLAN FOR A LINEAR PARK CONNECTING FIVE TOWNS
    $2,000.00;$2,000.00
    New Jersey; East Hanover Township Environmental Commission
  - East Harlem Council for Human Services, Inc. (08050826), 1980 September 01-1981 August 31 (Reel 4778)
    DEMON. PROJ. TO FOCUS ON AN OUTREACH EFFORT TO PRESUADE TEENAGERS (WHO ARE PREGNANT OR ARE MOTHERS) TO USE ITS HEALTH CARE FACILITY
    $15,066.00;$15,066.00
    Hunter, Marsha R.
    Harlem (New York, N.Y.); East Harlem Council for Human Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (09501235), 1995 July 01-1996 September 30 (Reel 8084)
    SUPPORT FOR PLANNING AN EMPLOYMENT-TRAINING PROGRAM
    $450,000.00;$450,000.00
    Elliott, Mark D.;Mincy, Ronald B.;Mohamed, Inca A.
    Boston (Mass.); New York (N.Y.); East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (09700253), 1996 October 01-2001 September 30 (Reel 9192)
    SUPPORT FOR IMPLEMENTATION AND EVALUATION OF THE ASAP EMPLOYMENT-TRAINING MODEL
    Human Development and Reproductive Health;Economic Development
    $2,500,000.00;$2,500,000.00
    Colborn, John L.
    United States; Boston (Mass.); New York (N.Y.); East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (09701789), 1997 September 01-1999 August 31 (Reel 8165;8750)
    SUPPORT FOR CAPACITY-BUILDING AND STRATEGIC PLANNING
    Human Development and Reproductive Health
    Mincy, Ronald B.
    United States; East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (09951836), 1999 August 01-2000 January 31 (Reel 8350)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PLANNING PHASE TO ESTABLISH A YOUTH OPPORTUNITY TRAINING INSTITUTE FOR RECIPIENTS OF FEDERAL YOUTH OPPORTUNITY GRANTS
    $84,500.00;$84,500.00
    Mincy, Ronald B.;Mohamed, Inca A.
    United States; Youth--Services for--United States; Labor supply--United States; East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (10001216), 2000 July 01-2001 December 31 (Reel 8636)
    TO SUPPORT PLANNING FOR A NATIONAL NETWORK OF STRIVE AFFILIATES IN ORDER TO SERVE MORE LOW-INCOME INDIVIDUALS AND INFLUENCE EMPLOYMENT POLICY
    Floyd, Virginia Davis;Manus, Mara A.
    United States; Labor supply--United States; Poor--Employment--United States; Youth--Employment--United States; East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Employment Services, Inc. (10200391), 2001 November 01-2002 October 31 (Reel 9092)
    For an intensive strategic planning process
    Economic Development;Human Development and Reproductive Health
    Manus, Mara A.;Floyd, Virginia Davis
    United States; Poor--United States--Employment; Labor supply--United States; East Harlem Employment Services, Inc.
  - East Harlem Music, Inc. (08450959), 1984 October 01-1986 June 30 (Reel 5586)
    SUPPORT FOR DEVELOPMENT OF NETWORK OF HARLEM-BASED CULTURAL ORGANIZATIONS FOCUSSING ON DROPOUT YOUTH
    $10,000.00;$10,000.00
    Mayleas, Ruth R.
    New York (N.Y.); East Harlem Music, Inc.
  - East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative (08351018), 1983 May 15-1983 November 14 (Reel 4498;5073)
    SUPPORT ON THE JOB TRAINING FOR TEN COOPERATIVE ORGANIZERS IN EAST JAVA
    Indonesia (Jakarta)
    $4,664.00;$4,664.00
    Sutoro, S. Ann
    Indonesia; East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative
  - East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative (08351019), 1983 August 05-1985 October 31 (Reel 5073;5253;5261)
    SUPPORT A TRAINING AND CONSULTANCY PROJECT IN EAST JAVA, INDONESIA
    $32,224.00;$31,737.90
    Djiwandono, Bianti
  - East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative (08650284), 1986 February 01-1987 January 31 (Reel 5236)
    TRAVEL COSTS FOR FIELD COORDINATORS AND SUPERVISORS OF THE COOPERATIVE (INDONESIA)
    $11,830.00;$9,249.20
  - East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative (09800880), 1998 March 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9018)
    SUPPORT FOR A DOCUMENTATION PROJECT ON WOMEN'S ECONOMIC PARTICIPATION THROUGH COOPERATIVES IN EAST JAVA
    Iskandar, Meiwita Budiharsana;Djiwandono, Bianti
    Indonesia; CoOperative societies -- Indonesia -- Jawa Timur Women -- Indonesia -- Jawa Timur -- Economic conditions; East Javanese Women's Central Cooperative
  - East Kalimantan Provincial Development Planning Agency (10250746), 2002 March 01-2004 February 29 (Reel 9098)
    For action research on the hand-over of natural resource management to local communities in East Kalimantan Regional Planning Board
    Antlov, Hans;Pradhan, Ujjwal
    Indonesia; Natural resources--Management--Indonesia; Local government--Indonesia; East Kalimantan Provincial Development Planning Agency
  - East Liberty Development, Incorporated (08300635), 1983 July 01-1987 June 30 (Reel 5460)
    PARTIAL GENERAL SUPPORT TO ENABLE IT TO EXPAND ITS DEVELOPMENT ACTIVITIES
    $156,000.00;$156,000.00
    Howard, Craig
    Pittsburgh (Pa.); East Liberty Development, Incorporated
  - East Little Havana Community Development Corporation (08650999), 1986 July 01-1987 July 31 (Reel 5467)
    Miami (Fla.); East Little Havana Community Development Corporation
  - East Little Havana Community Development Corporation (08751122), 1987 July 01-1987 December 31 (Reel 5427)
    SUPPORT FOR CORE OPERATING EXPENSES